[{"answer": " Could you ever conceive of going to that place, my friend, persuade my son to come home?  I'd pay you.  I'd pay you 1000 dollars", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Good. Now you can go for a reason", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What are you doing in my friend", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Passing through! You're so white. Did you ever see a guy so white, my friend?  my friend, actually", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Did you forget where I live? It's four o'clock", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You just woke up", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Bird. That's jazz", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I don't know. What's the name of your sailboat", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You'd say if you mind", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "my friend, you like everybody", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "No, I like him", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I don't like you", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " Bastard!  Isn't it great, my friend? I found it in that place.  I bargained for about two weeks", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh, it was", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Could we sail to that place", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I have to go to that place", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What does he say", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You've got to get a new jacket. Really. You must be sick of the same clothes. I'm sick of seeing you in them", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I'll go", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yesterday you're ogling girls on the terrace, today you're getting married. It's absurd", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You love me and you're not marrying me", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I love my friend", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " my friend, I don't love you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "At Christmas. To that place with Freddie Miles and", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Everybody knows Freddie Miles", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "And tomorrow", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I know the my friend di Spagna. What time", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I really don't want to see anybody", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Even her", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Even her", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What about my friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "November, I thought", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "November 7th is my information", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "It's not a pattern, it's a coincidence. There must be fifty hotels in that place, there must have been a hundred people renting a boat on that day", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "31 people", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "It is a little coarse, yes", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I have", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Sorry.  N", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "You have, yes", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " No.  By the way, officially there are no Italian homosexuals. Makes my friend, my friend very inconvenient", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " Il signor my friend ha una fidanzata, il signor my friend ha una fidanzata e probabilmente il signor that place ha molte fidanzate", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " Hello my friend, so good to see you", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": " my friend", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Mr my friend", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I'm well, thank you", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Hardly. I couldn't be less alone", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Of course.  Aunt my friend", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "I've thought about you", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "You know what", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": " my friend? I haven't seen him in months.  No, I'm alone.", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Good. But I think we should stay in here for the rest of the trip", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": " Was who my friend", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Was that my friend", "docId": "mr-ripley_shooting.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "my friend. You were kissing somebody. Looked like my friend", "qsentId": 56}]